<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Baigel Bytes</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/</link><description>Recent content on Baigel Bytes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why I stopped identifying with religion and spirituality, but still take an interest in them as an outsider.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/non-religious/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/non-religious/</guid><description>Introduction: Firstly, let me apologise in advance about the length of this post. If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this on a mobile device it might end up feeling like a book but hopefully you&amp;rsquo;re here because you like reading in which case I hope you find this post entertaining, informative and enjoyable :)
I was raised in a Muslim family, for the majority of my childhood and the entirety of my teenage years, by my grandparents.</description></item><item><title>More mental and physical health tips from journeys past &amp; present.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh2/</guid><description>Introduction: Have you ever woken up from sleep with a sharp pain in your ear? One so sharp, so intense that you can&amp;rsquo;t even lift your head off the pillow without quietly (so as not to wake your flatmates) shreeking in pain.
This is something that&amp;rsquo;s happend to me many times and continues to happen to me to this day. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to look into it sometime but for now I&amp;rsquo;m using it as part of the inspiration for this article.</description></item><item><title>Vegans, why calling people murderers and rapists isn't the best way to get them to listen to your arguments.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/vegans/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/vegans/</guid><description>Reason cannot be cultivated in a mind consumed by emotions. Yes, I agree with the ethics and moral standing of the vegan argument. It is not right to take the lives of sentient beings that have the same desire as us to enjoy life and procreate. Yes, I and many other meat eaters agree that factory farming is abhorent at the very least and alternatives methods of cultivating animal based protiens, if people insist upon or require them for health reasons, need to be devised and implimented.</description></item><item><title>There is no center of the Universe! (Topics I can't compute - part 2)</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/ticc2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/ticc2/</guid><description>This is part 2 in the series, Topics I can&amp;rsquo;t compute. As the name sugguests this series deals with topics I either partially or completely don&amp;rsquo;t understand or that are so mind blowing that I find them hard to wrap my head around. Hopefully your brains don&amp;rsquo;t get completely fried XD. Enjoy :)
Are you ready to have your mind blown? Our entire universe could be the 3 dimensional surface of a four dimensional hypersphere!</description></item><item><title>Capitalism. Where anyone can become rich, but not everyone.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/capitalism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/capitalism/</guid><description>Why the rich get richer and the poor get poorer: It&amp;rsquo;s not exclusively the governments fault: Not exclusivley I said!
Yes its a fact, a frustratingly sad fact that a lot of the richest people in the world pay little to no taxes. I agree this is absolutely not ok and should change so they start giving their fair share!
However, we - and I include myself in this - are also at least partly to blame.</description></item><item><title>Arguments for the possibility of a created universe.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/deismpossible/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/deismpossible/</guid><description>Why I think scientists and atheists shouldn&amp;rsquo;t say there can&amp;rsquo;t be a God or that there definitely isn&amp;rsquo;t one. Introduction: One thing that religious people often say is &amp;lsquo;There just has to be a creator&amp;rsquo;. Atheists will be quick to point out that this isn&amp;rsquo;t technically true. But some atheists commit the same mistake when they (sometimes proudly) proclaim that their is no god or that nothing happens after we die besides us going into the ground and our bodies getting eaten by insects.</description></item><item><title>Free will might just be an illusion! (Topics I can't compute - part 1)</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/freewill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/freewill/</guid><description>This is part one of a series called: Topics I can&amp;rsquo;t compute. As the name sugguests posts in this series will cover topics that I either partially or completely don&amp;rsquo;t understand or that are so mind blowing that I find them hard to wrap my head around.
Free Will vs Determinism. A thought experiment: Is free will real? Some philosophers think not.
Think of your favourite food, let&amp;rsquo;s say for example you absolutely love steak!</description></item><item><title>Support Baigel Bytes</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/supportme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/supportme/</guid><description>Help me turn this into a career. I&amp;rsquo;d like to do blogging and life coaching full time without the need for a 9-5 because this is where my passions lie!
I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to write books many times before at different points in my life but my interests have always shifted from one subject to another. Blogging is perfect for this as I can literally write about any subject I like.</description></item><item><title>Mental Health Issues, some Self Help Tips.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh/</guid><description>Introduction: Disclaimer: I am not a medical professional. The points of advice I&amp;rsquo;m about to give in this article are not medical advice, if you are experiencing symptoms of any medical conditions please seek professional advice from your GP. The tips I list below can however be used in addition to any professional medical advice you recieve from your doctor so long as they approve. Thank you :)
Considering all of the near infinite crazyness that&amp;rsquo;s been happening over the last decade (I&amp;rsquo;m reffering off course to that year that shall not be named which felt like a decade.</description></item><item><title>Why Muslims often get offended when you criticise their religion.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/religiousidentity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/religiousidentity/</guid><description>Some ideas for more respectful discussions. Introduction: I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching young atheists and x-Muslims debating Muslims for a while now and I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed a slight trend. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this happens when atheists and people of other faiths have debates but what happens is that whenever Islam is criticized as an ideology, even when they explicitly state they are not criticising any individuals that follow the faith but just the faith itself, Muslims inevitably get offended and often the atheist is labelled as an islamaphobe.</description></item></channel></rss>