<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Baigel Bytes</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/</link><description>Recent content on Baigel Bytes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arguments for the possibility of a created universe.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/deismpossible/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/deismpossible/</guid><description>Why I think scientists and atheists shouldn&amp;rsquo;t say there can&amp;rsquo;t be a God or that there definitely isn&amp;rsquo;t one. Introduction: One thing that religious people often say is &amp;lsquo;There just has to be a creator&amp;rsquo;. Atheists will be quick to point out that this isn&amp;rsquo;t technically true. But some atheists commit the same mistake when they (sometimes proudly) proclaim that their is no god or that nothing happens after we die besides us going into the ground and our bodies getting eaten by insects.</description></item><item><title>Free will might just be an illusion! (Topics I can't compute - part 1)</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/freewill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/freewill/</guid><description>This is part one of a series called: Topics I can&amp;rsquo;t compute. As the name sugguests posts in this series will cover topics that I either partially or completely don&amp;rsquo;t understand or that are so mind blowing that I find them hard to wrap my head around.
Free Will vs Determinism. A thought experiment: Is free will real? Some philosophers think not.
Think of your favourite food, let&amp;rsquo;s say for example you absolutely love steak!</description></item><item><title>Support Baigel Bytes</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/supportme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/supportme/</guid><description>Help me turn this into a career. I&amp;rsquo;d like to do blogging and life coaching full time without the need for a 9-5 because this is where my passions lie!
I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to write books many times before at different points in my life but my interests have always shifted from one subject to another. Blogging is perfect for this as I can literally write about any subject I like.</description></item><item><title>Mental Health Issues, some Self Help Tips.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh/</guid><description>Introduction: Disclaimer: I am not a medical professional. The points of advice I&amp;rsquo;m about to give in this article are not medical advice, if you are experiencing symptoms of any medical conditions please seek professional advice from your GP. The tips I list below can however be used in addition to any professional medical advice you recieve from your doctor so long as they approve. Thank you :)
Considering all of the near infinite crazyness that&amp;rsquo;s been happening over the last decade (I&amp;rsquo;m reffering off course to that year that shall not be named which felt like a decade.</description></item><item><title>Why Muslims often get offended when you criticise their religion.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/religiousidentity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/religiousidentity/</guid><description>Some ideas for more respectful discussions. Introduction: I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching young atheists and x-Muslims debating Muslims for a while now and I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed a slight trend. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this happens when atheists and people of other faiths have debates but what happens is that whenever Islam is criticized as an ideology, even when they explicitly state they are not criticising any individuals that follow the faith but just the faith itself, Muslims inevitably get offended and often the atheist is labelled as an islamaphobe.</description></item><item><title>About me:</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/about/</guid><description>I used to be an IT guy, I left the industry in search of something different. I go through phases where I&amp;rsquo;m into different topics and subjects so the subjects and topics I make posts about on here will change over time and not be devoted to just one single area of interest.
I&amp;rsquo;m an aspie, I believe the pc term is now, &amp;lsquo;high functioning autism&amp;rsquo; though I&amp;rsquo;m not much of a fan of that description as it might lead some people to think that I might be some kind of genius when really, I&amp;rsquo;m just your avarage Adnan :).</description></item><item><title>Life Coaching</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/lifecoaching/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/lifecoaching/</guid><description>What can life coaching do for you? Life coaching is life changing, plain and simple! Right from the outset you will gain clarity on what your goals and dreams are (If you&amp;rsquo;re not already clear about them that is.) and what you can do right now to start achieving them.
Then together, we will create a unique plan to ensure you keep making consistent progress towards your goals whilst removing any blocks you might encounter along the way.</description></item></channel></rss>