<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Philosophy on Baigel Bytes</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/tags/philosophy/</link><description>Recent content in Philosophy on Baigel Bytes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/tags/philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vegans, why calling people murderers and rapists isn't the best way to get them to listen to your arguments.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/vegans/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/vegans/</guid><description>Reason cannot be cultivated in a mind consumed by emotions. Yes, I agree with the ethics and moral standing of the vegan argument. It is not right to take the lives of sentient beings that have the same desire as us to enjoy life and procreate. Yes, I and many other meat eaters agree that factory farming is abhorent at the very least and alternatives methods of cultivating animal based protiens, if people insist upon or require them for health reasons, need to be devised and implimented.</description></item><item><title>Free will might just be an illusion! (Topics I can't compute - part 1)</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/freewill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/freewill/</guid><description>This is part one of a series called: Topics I can&amp;rsquo;t compute. As the name sugguests posts in this series will cover topics that I either partially or completely don&amp;rsquo;t understand or that are so mind blowing that I find them hard to wrap my head around.
Free Will vs Determinism. A thought experiment: Is free will real? Some philosophers think not.
Think of your favourite food, let&amp;rsquo;s say for example you absolutely love steak!</description></item><item><title>Why Muslims often get offended when you criticise their religion.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/religiousidentity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/religiousidentity/</guid><description>Some ideas for more respectful discussions. Introduction: I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching young atheists and x-Muslims debating Muslims for a while now and I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed a slight trend. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this happens when atheists and people of other faiths have debates but what happens is that whenever Islam is criticized as an ideology, even when they explicitly state they are not criticising any individuals that follow the faith but just the faith itself, Muslims inevitably get offended and often the atheist is labelled as an islamaphobe.</description></item></channel></rss>