<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Religion on Baigel Bytes</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/tags/religion/</link><description>Recent content in Religion on Baigel Bytes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/tags/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why I stopped identifying with religion and spirituality, but still take an interest in them as an outsider.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/non-religious/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/non-religious/</guid><description>Introduction: Firstly, let me apologise in advance about the length of this post. If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this on a mobile device it might end up feeling like a book but hopefully you&amp;rsquo;re here because you like reading in which case I hope you find this post entertaining, informative and enjoyable :)
I was raised in a Muslim family, for the majority of my childhood and the entirety of my teenage years, by my grandparents.</description></item><item><title>Why Muslims often get offended when you criticise their religion.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/religiousidentity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/religiousidentity/</guid><description>Some ideas for more respectful discussions. Introduction: I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching young atheists and x-Muslims debating Muslims for a while now and I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed a slight trend. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if this happens when atheists and people of other faiths have debates but what happens is that whenever Islam is criticized as an ideology, even when they explicitly state they are not criticising any individuals that follow the faith but just the faith itself, Muslims inevitably get offended and often the atheist is labelled as an islamaphobe.</description></item></channel></rss>