<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Self Awareness on Baigel Bytes</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/tags/self-awareness/</link><description>Recent content in Self Awareness on Baigel Bytes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&lt;a href="https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/tags/self-awareness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>More mental and physical health tips from journeys past &amp; present.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh2/</guid><description>Introduction: Have you ever woken up from sleep with a sharp pain in your ear? One so sharp, so intense that you can&amp;rsquo;t even lift your head off the pillow without quietly (so as not to wake your flatmates) shreeking in pain.
This is something that&amp;rsquo;s happend to me many times and continues to happen to me to this day. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to look into it sometime but for now I&amp;rsquo;m using it as part of the inspiration for this article.</description></item><item><title>Mental Health Issues, some Self Help Tips.</title><link>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://baigelbytes.github.io/lifecoachbaig/blog/mh/</guid><description>Introduction: Disclaimer: I am not a medical professional. The points of advice I&amp;rsquo;m about to give in this article are not medical advice, if you are experiencing symptoms of any medical conditions please seek professional advice from your GP. The tips I list below can however be used in addition to any professional medical advice you recieve from your doctor so long as they approve. Thank you :)
Considering all of the near infinite crazyness that&amp;rsquo;s been happening over the last decade (I&amp;rsquo;m reffering off course to that year that shall not be named which felt like a decade.</description></item></channel></rss>